http://www.macola.com/privacy-statement

HomePrivacy Statement
Enhancing Order Entry, Inventory & Supply Chain Management.
Macola 10.7
See Features »
June 2013
ECi Holding N.V., along with its subsidiaries, divisions, and affiliates ("ECi"), understands the importance of protecting and safeguarding your privacy when you use our web site. This privacy statement tells you about the information ECi may collect on this web site, how the information is used, and how you can access and correct certain information that we may collect.
If you as a visitor choose to register or submit information to ECi via this web site (the “Site”), you agree to the use of such data in accordance with this privacy statement. Please note that this Site contains links to other web sites, including, without limitation, web sites maintained by ECi, and other affiliated entities of ECi . Also note that the ECi may use third parties to host all or portions of, or to assist in maintaining, the ECi web sites.
If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, or do not feel that your concerns have been addressed, please direct your questions to using the appropriate email link set forth in the “Contact Us” section below.
Collection of Your Personal Information. You can access many areas of our web site without submitting any personally identifiable information. You may voluntarily choose to provide ECi with identifiable personal data by completing forms, sending emails, or other means as may be provided from time to time on the Site. The personally identifiable information that we would collect from you if you so choose would typically include your name and title, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone and fax numbers, and information about your company. In addition to information that you voluntarily submit, ECi may, at its option, collect additional information about you from third party sources. Personal Information collected by ECi will be as reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and to provide the most relevant, targeted offers and information from ECi and for no other purpose. All such information collected shall be referred to herein as “Personal Information”. Furthermore, ECi monitors incoming and outgoing Site traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers and to administer its Site. ECi also uses this data to assemble broad demographic information about its visitors, customers, and partners in general.
We do not usually seek sensitive information (for example, data relating to race or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, criminal record, physical or mental health or sexual orientation) from Site visitors. We will, where necessary, obtain your explicit consent to collect and use such information. The following is a list of examples where you may choose to specifically and voluntarily submit Personal Information to ECi through this Site, which ECi may use for each purpose(s) as you indicate at the time of your submission:
Request a copy of ECi’s annual report or other publications;
Register for access to certain areas of the Site;
Contact us for further information about products, services, events, and programs or to submit questions or comments to ECi;
Subscribe to receive newsletters, information, alerts, offers, and other communications;
Submit a resume and/or job application for possible employment with ECi;
Participate in surveys, quizzes, promotions, and contests as may be available on the Site from time to time; and/or
Register for attendance or sponsorship at events and conferences.
Use of Your Personal Information. ECi uses Personal Information submitted through the Site to provide a way for customers, partners, customer and partner prospects, and other contacts to communicate with our team. ECi collects the Personal Information from you in order to establish and maintain relationships, and in order to serve you better. When appropriate, ECi may also use the Personal Information separately or in combination with pre-existing information.
By voluntarily submitting your Personal Information, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Information as described in this Policy Statement. In some circumstances, ECi may share Personal Information that you voluntarily submit with trustworthy business partners. We will only use such third party business partners in order to deliver services to us or on our behalf, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
Personal Information collected on this Site may be stored and processed in the Netherlands, the United States, Canada, or any other country in which ECi (or its affiliates, subsidiaries, and divisions and their respective third party business partners and suppliers) maintain facilities. This may include transfer to countries without data protection rules similar to those in effect in your country of residence. You acknowledge and agree that by providing Personal Information to ECi through this Site, you consent to the transmission of such Personal Information over international borders as necessary for processing your requests.
Due to the existing legal, regulatory, and security environment, ECi may be required, under certain circumstances, to disclose aggregate level and/or personally identifiable information submitted to ECi through the Site. ECi will use reasonable efforts to limit such disclosures to the following circumstances: (i) where ECi believes in good faith that it is required to do so in response to a subpoena or other legal process; (ii) where reasonably required to do so in order to maintain, update or otherwise implement ECi’s data security measures, equipment, technical operations and the like; (iii) where reasonably necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities to preserve and/or enforce ECi’s rights, including but not limited to enforcing the Terms of Use for this Site; (iv) protect and defend the rights or property of ECi; or (v) in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of the public or of users of the ECi products, services, and the Site.
In addition, ECi may also disclose Personal Information in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the ECi business or any part thereof, or as part of a security audit.
Protection of Your Personal Information.ECi undertakes substantial efforts to protect the confidentiality of the Personal Information, preferences and other information it has collected through this Site and will never knowingly allow access to this information to anyone outside ECi other than as described herein. ECi has made a substantial investment in its server, database, backup and firewall technologies to protect the information assets of the ECi network, including the confidentiality of Personal Information collected through this Site. These technologies are deployed as part of a sophisticated security architecture and protocol.
You should also do your part in protecting your information. Your ECi username and any password (if such is provided or enacted) are confidential, and we recommend that you not divulge them to anyone. Unfortunately, due to the nature of the Internet as a public transmission network, neither ECi’s network nor data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect Personal Information that is transmitted to us by you, ECi cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information. Thus, any Personal Information transmitted to us is done so at your own risk. Once we receive Personal Information, ECi undertakes substantial efforts to protect the confidentiality of this information consistent with this Privacy Statement.
Cookies. If you review or download information, we may track the visit through the use of "cookies". Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you will find cookies at most major web sites. Cookies help ECi to tailor information to your preferences and to see which areas of the web site are frequented most. ECi never uses cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can change your browser settings to refuse cookies. However, in so doing, you may not be able to fully utilize the Site.
Web Beacons. Pages on this Site may contain electronic images referred to as Web Beacons and also sometimes referred to as single-pixel gifs or clear gifs. The Web Beacons may be used to assist in delivering cookies throughout our Site to track the number of users and Site activity tracking purposes.
Links to Other Web Sites. This Site may contain links to web sites which are owned and operated by third parties and do not operate in accordance with this Privacy Statement. When you link to other web sites through this Site, this Privacy Statement and our privacy practices no longer apply. We encourage you to review each site’s privacy policy before disclosing any personally identifiable information. ECi is not responsible for the privacy practices of such third party web sites.
Choices Regarding Use of Personal Information. Upon voluntarily providing your Personal Information to ECi through this Site, ECi will use your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Should you at any time decide that you do not want to continue to receive electronic communications, you will have the ability to unsubscribe or “opt out” from such communications by means of a link provided in each such communication, or if not provided therein, by sending an email or contacting us at the contact details provided in the Contact Us section of this Privacy Statement.
Corrections, Access and Updates to Your Personal Information. ECi aims to keep your Personal Information as accurate as possible. Should you at any time desire to review, correct or update your Personal Information, you may update your relevant profile or registration (when applicable) or contact us using the contact information outlined in the Contact Us section below; ECi will comply with such requests as soon as commercially reasonable. In order to ensure the safety of Personal Information, please note you will be subject to providing sufficient evidence of your identity at the time of any such request before any Personal Information records will be made available by ECi.
Data Retention. The Personal Information that you submit to ECi will only be retained for as long as is requires for the purposes for which it was collected or as required by law. Our retention of your Personal Information allows ECi to continue to provide you with highly personalized services without interruption.
Changes to this Privacy Statement. ECi reserves the right to change this policy at any time and without prior notice to you. Please check the Privacy Statement frequently for changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. ECi will take reasonable measures to notify you if there is a material change in our privacy practices with respect to use of the information you have provided to ECi. ECi will conspicuously post these changes in our Privacy Policy. ECi also will post a message on the home page of its Web site that states that the Privacy Policy has been changed, and will provide a link to the Privacy Policy.
Aviso de privacidad de ECi de México, S.A. de C.V. y sus miembros afiliados, y partes relacionadas.
De conformidad en lo dispuesto por la Ley Federal de Protección de Datos Personales en Posesión de Particulares, se emite el presente Aviso de Privacidad en los siguientes términos:
DEFINICIONES: (i) Aviso de privacidad: El presente documento, según dicho término se define en el inciso I. Del artículo 3 de la ley; (ii) Ley: Ley Federal de Protección de Datos Personales en Posesión de Particulares; Reglamento: Reglamento a la Ley Federal de Protección de Datos Personales en Posesión de Particulares; (iii) Responsable: ECi de México, S.A. de C.V., y/o sus afiliadas y/o filiales internacionales y/o partes relacionadas; y (iv) Afiliada: significa, con respecto a cualquier socio, cualquier persona que directa o indirectamente tenga el control de o sea controlada por dicho socio, o junto con dicho socio, esté bajo el control común de esa persona. Para efectos de esta definición, el término “control” (que incluye, con un significado correlativo, los términos “controlando”, “controlada por” y “bajo el control común con”), utilizado con respecto a cualquier socio, significará la facultad directa o indirecta, de dirigir o determinar la dirección de la administración o políticas de dicha parte, sea a través de la propiedad de partes sociales con derecho a voto, por contrato o de cualquier otra forma.
IDENTIDAD Y DOMICILIO DEL RESPONSABLE DE LOS DATOS PERSONALES: Para efectos del presente Aviso de Privacidad, ECi de México, S.A. de C.V. y sus miembros afiliados y/o filiales internacionales (en adelante el “EL RESPONSABLE”), señalan como encargado de la obtención, divulgación, almacenamiento, uso, incluido acción de acceso, manejo, aprovechamiento, transferencia o disposición de datos personales (en adelante el “Tratamiento”) al Comité de Privacidad designado por EL RESPONSABLE, (en lo sucesivo el “Comité de Privacidad”), con domicilio en Avenida Mariano Otero, 1249 Local B-243 Colonia Rinconada del Bosque, Guadalajara, Jalisco, México, CP 44530.
INFORMACIÓN A RECABAR Y FINALIDADES DEL TRATAMIENTO DE DATOS PERSONALES: Le informamos que EL RESPONSABLE podrá recopilar su información a través de diferentes fuentes, ya sea Personal y/o Directamente proporcionados por el Titular o Indirectamente por cualquier otra fuente de información comercialmente disponibles o que sean permitidas por la Ley. La colecta y Tratamiento de datos personales del Titular, incluyendo los datos personales sensibles que en su caso lleguemos a recabar, y salvo que el Titular disponga lo contrario mediante el medio descrito en el presente Aviso de Privacidad, tiene como finalidad, la evaluación de solicitudes de empleo, contratación de empleados, evaluación de contratistas, propuestas y contratación con proveedores de servicios y productos, elaboración y manejo de contratos comerciales, procesos de pago, así como para el cumplimiento con nuestras obligaciones laborales, administrativas, comerciales y fiscales establecimiento de bases de datos de proveedores, desarrollo de nuevos productos y servicios, asesoría, comercialización, promoción, contratación y colocación de todo tipo de servicios y productos y/o mejora de nuestros productos y servicios y otras obligaciones derivadas de cualquier relación jurídica entre el titular de datos personales y EL RESPONSABLE o las empresas afiliadas y subsidiarias de EL RESPONSABLE. Sus datos personales, también podrán tener, entre otras, las siguientes finalidades: (i) Atender requerimientos legales de autoridades competentes; (ii) Hacer de su conocimiento, la gama de nuevos productos y servicios, así como beneficios, descuentos, promociones, estudios de mercado, promociones, notificaciones sobre cambio en condiciones y en general toda la publicidad derivada de los productos y servicios que ofrece EL RESPONSABLE y/o las empresas afiliadas y subsidiarias de EL RESPONSABLE; (iii) Análisis y desarrollo de productos y de proveedores así como el uso de nuestros productos y servicios; y (iv) Para el cumplimiento de nuestros términos y condiciones con relación a nuestras obligaciones, convenios, contratos, así como para el desarrollo de productos, venta de productos o la prestación de nuestros servicios; y (v) en su caso, para el uso de nuestras áreas de recursos humanos y compras, de conformidad a las políticas de estas últimas. Los datos sensibles que se pudieran recabar podrán ser utilizados para el mejor cumplimiento de nuestros objetivos legales, fiscales o comerciales.
OPCIONES Y MEDIOS QUE EL RESPONSABLE, OFRECE A LOS TITULARES DE DATOS PERSONALES PARA LIMITAR EL USO O DIVULGACIÓN DE SU INFORMACIÓN: Los datos personales del titular, serán mantenidos en estricta confidencialidad, de conformidad con las medidas de seguridad, administrativas, técnicas y físicas que al efecto EL RESPONSABLE ha implementado y las que en el futuro implemente en sus políticas y procedimientos de seguridad, quedando prohibido su divulgación ilícita y limitando su uso a terceros, conforme a lo previsto en el presente Aviso de Privacidad.
MEDIOS PARA EL EJERCICIO DE DERECHOS DEL TITULAR: El titular de datos personales, podrá ejercer sus derechos de acceso, rectificación, cancelación, posición, limitación de uso, divulgación o revocación, mediante solicitud por escrito enviada vía correo postal o correo electrónico dirigidos a:
Por correo postal o mensajería privada:
Comité de Privacidad de EL RESPONSABLE en Avenida Mariano Otero1249 Local B-243 Colonia Rinconada del BosqueGuadalajara, Jalisco, México, CP 44530
Con copia para: Departamento Legal de EL RESPONSABLE:
Florencia 2454 Colonia Lomas de Providenciaen Guadalajara, Jalisco, México, CP 44647
Por correo electrónico a: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Mediante solicitud por escrito que contenga la siguiente información: (i) El nombre completo del titular de los datos personales, domicilio y cuenta de correo electrónico, para poder comunicarle la respuesta a su solicitud; (ii) Los documentos que acrediten la identidad y en su caso la representación legal del titular de los datos personales; (iii) La descripción clara y precisa de los datos personales respecto de los que se busca ejercer alguno de los derechos antes mencionados; (iv) Cualquier otro elemento o documento que facilite la localización de los datos personales; y (v) En el caso de solicitudes de rectificación de datos personales, el titular, deberá indicar, las modificaciones a realizarse y aportar la documentación que sustente su petición.
TRANSFERENCIA DE DATOS PERSONALES.
EL RESPONSABLE podrá realizar la transferencia de datos a: (i) Las empresas afiliadas y subsidiarias de EL RESPONSABLE a nivel internacional; (ii) Terceros proveedores de servicios para el cumplimiento de las obligaciones legales adquiridas por EL RESPONSABLE o por cualquiera de las empresas afiliadas y subsidiarias de EL RESPONSABLE; (iii) Terceros proveedores de servicios de investigación, análisis de datos, envío de información enfocada a las necesidades del titular de datos personales, así como en la realización de otros servicios financieros necesarios o requeridos por el titular de datos personales; (iv) Socios comerciales con los que EL RESPONSABLE o cualquiera de las empresas de EL RESPONSABLE, lleve a cabo convenios o contratos enfocados al desarrollo de nuevos productos y/o servicios enfocados al mejoramiento y de acuerdo a sus necesidades e investigación; (v) Terceros derivado de un reestructura corporativa, incluyendo, la fusión, consolidación, venta, liquidación o transferencia de activos; y (vi) Otras transmisiones previstas en la Ley citada y su Reglamento.
Los terceros y las entidades receptores de datos personales, asumen las mismas obligaciones y/o responsabilidades de EL RESPONSABLE, de conformidad con lo descrito en el presente Aviso de Privacidad.
El titular de datos personales que presenta cualquier solicitud para entablar una relación jurídica con EL RESPONSABLE o por cualquiera de las empresas de EL RESPONSABLE, acepta la transferencia de sus datos personales, en los términos descritos en el presente Aviso de Privacidad.
CAMBIOS AL AVISO DE PRIVACIDAD: Cualquier cambio al presente aviso de privacidad, le será informado a través de cualquiera de los siguientes medios: (i) Avisos en las oficinas de EL RESPONSABLE; (ii) Avisos en el portal de Internet de EL RESPONSABLE (www.exact.com); y (iii) Cualquier otro medio de comunicación público o privado previstos en los contratos que amparan las operaciones celebradas entre EL RESPONSABLE o por cualquiera de las empresas de EL RESPONSABLE.
El Comité de Privacidad será en todo tiempo conformado por representantes de áreas funcionales y designados por ECi de México, S.A. de C.V.
Fecha ultima de actualización 01/02/2013.
